<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Procedural Recipes</title><link>http://diegoarjz.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Procedural Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 18:16:19 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://diegoarjz.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Curriculum Vitæ</title><link>http://diegoarjz.github.io/cv/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 19:03:36 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://diegoarjz.github.io/cv/</guid><description>Skills C&amp;#43;&amp;#43;11/14/17 Urban Procedural Modeling Object Oriented Programming Agile Software Development Python Javascript Coffeescript Computer Graphics OpenGL, glsl, webGL Three.js Universal Scene Description Git Cmake, Ninja Urban Reconstruction Experience June 2020 - Now Senior Software Engineer Foundry Development of Nuke&amp;#39;s Hydra Viewer.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://diegoarjz.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 19:02:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://diegoarjz.github.io/about/</guid><description>Who am I? I’m Diego and I’m a software engineer who has a taken an interest in procedural modelling around 2012 when I started my PhD. Now I want to contribute to the open source community with implementations of stuff I have learnt.
What is this page about? One of my pet projects is Pagoda which is a graph based framework for general purpose 3D procedural modelling. I want this page to be a collection of my development work in Pagoda and examples of how it can be used to create content.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Simple Building</title><link>http://diegoarjz.github.io/posts/creating-a-simple-building/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 18:16:19 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://diegoarjz.github.io/posts/creating-a-simple-building/</guid><description>I decided to start my series of posts with an example of how we can create a simple building using pagoda. Hopefully this will help understand how pagoda can be used to generate 3D content.
Pagoda has a graph based approach to defining the rules with which we can generate our models. This means that nodes in this graph create, modify or otherwise perform any sort of operation on our objects and edges define the flow of objects between nodes.</description></item></channel></rss>